Is everything ok? I'm not sure how the audio is working or anything.
Let's wait a little bit.
Okay.
What should we do?
Good evening.
Your hand gesture is very unique.
Hey, Yuna, your hand gesture is a little..,
It doesn't show? Yuna's hand gesture is kind of mysterious.
I see.
Yuna.
Yuna. Yuna is Yuna.
Did you always do it like this?
No, I noticed it when you said it earlier today.
Maybe it's on the screen.
Is it on the screen?
Your hands are big.
My hands are big.
Indeed. Indeed.
They are big.
Oh, it's true. They are big.
Yes, it is.
Wow. Oh, I wonder if I'm ready now. Good evening.
Yes. Shall we say hello?
Yes.
Yes. Good evening. The morning chime has rung. We.
I know, I'm Shiruchu, the opposite.
It's ebichu, reversed.
That's it, isn't it? It's Ebichu from now on.
We've decided that we're going to do it by refusing to pose as Ebichu.
Oh, really?
Is that so?
Oh, oh.
That one.
That? You mean with that?
Yeah. That's it.
Yeah.
I just did it out of sight.
That's what I meant.
Indeed.
Which one of us is going to be in power in the piece world?
First place.
I've already decided to decline.
There's absolutely nothing clumsy or stupid about the pose.
Please, everyone, don't make waves.
Really.
You say that a lot. They say that choreography is something they have to worry about because they can't get copyrights.
Ah.
It seems that they can't get the rights to the movements.
That's true.
The other day, I saw Genjib's new song on TikTok.
It's really easy to understand...you know, 10,000 songs in the Alps.
I don't even know how far back I should go if I am told about the rights.
But, you know, easy-to-understand poses.
But, you know, if you do a lot of poses,
But, you know, if you do a lot of poses, you may find yourself thinking, "I've done a similar pose before," right?
Yes, we have.
We had a lesson today,
We have a PE teacher named Ikue-sensei, who is a dance teacher,
She has a choreography that usually looks like this, doesn't it?
And then there's a certain song and another song we're going to play.
I'm not going to reveal either of them, but one song and the other song are similar, in shape.
I'm not going to reveal either of them. So, the form of the choreography?
Like, do you start from the right foot or the left foot?
One is superhero, but the superhero goes out on the right foot,
One is like a superhero, but the superhero goes out on the right foot, but on some songs, he goes out on the left foot.
You were almost caught in a trap earlier.
That's how it is.
We are currently on our spring tour.
Yes.
Yes, we are.
Our first tour.
First tour.
Yes, first tour.
How do you like it? How's it going? You've done 11 shows now?
We have...
We have... 5 shows left.
5 shows, so we've done 12 shows.
That's fast.
Only 5 more shows.
Only 5 more shows. I don't really feel like there are only 5 more shows.
It's so fast.
It's so fast, isn't it?
I think this is the first time for you to go on a tour with space. How are you guys doing?
How are you doing?
How are you doing, Mr. Numa?
Well, at first I thought we were going to do so many shows, but when I heard that we have 5 more shows to go, I thought it's going to be very fast.
Yes, I guess so.
But what I like the most is that our food is so delicious.
Oh, hey.
I get fat.
You don't get fat, do you, junior high school students?
No, I don't.
Swollen.
What?
Do you?
We're still in our teens, you know.
But, really, I have never been to many prefectures or regions before entering space.Well, but really, I had never been to many prefectures or regions before I entered space.
I had never been to many prefectures or regions before I entered space.
That's right.
That's why it was so challenging, wasn't it?
I am glad to have eaten so many different kinds of food.
Was there anything in particular that left a lasting impression on you? I'm sure you'll be asked that.
Oh, um, the DRAKING in Fukuoka.
Draking.
It was so delicious.
It's delicious.
It's a dorayaki with whipped cream and no strawberries.
Hey.
Huh? What about Yunan?
Was it good?
Uh, the tour?
Let me ask you what was good. What was good?
What was good?
The sushi restaurant in Hokkaido.
Sushi and seafood, sushi and seafood,
The next day, I ate seafood,
Seafood?
I was surprised that the salmon roe was so delicious.
It's totally different from salmon roe.
It's kind of sticky.
Oh.
It's like a sticky feeling.
Yes, yes.
I often use the word "sticky" in sushi.
Hee.
It's an exchange meal.
From a girl.
Don't you know? Mr. Fujii.
She likes sushi so much that she takes a sushi class.
What?
I used to eat sushi all the time.
I thought it was ramen.
The economy got worse and worse.
I'm not going to do it.
That's not true.
It's made of sushi because of Mr. Fujii's selfishness.
I see.
Even if it's good food.
That sounds good.
What? How are the live performances?
I'm getting used to it.
I mean, at first,
I'm really nervous,
You are nervous?
I'm extremely nervous.
I need someone to say something like that to me so I can get out there.
Everyone does it,
It's a live routine,
We Nakayama,
Meditate first,
Then it's Nakayama time.
Then, we get up a little bit,
and then perform,
and stand up on the sleeve,
I have a few things to say,
You know, the younger kids..,
They're slapping each other on the back, right?
I don't understand what that means.
Didn't they used to do that?
We used to do that,
I only did it a few times,
Were you one of those people who didn't do it much?
Why, because people used to slap me on the back,
I don't like to stand on stage like that.
It makes me feel like I'm being punched in the back.
Because it hurts,
It hurts, so I feel like I'm getting into it.
When you get hit, you feel it on your back,
I feel it like a "bang".
Wow.
It tightens up.
Sometimes, I get a slap on the back,
I get spit into my organs,
After that,
I hate it.
No?
Yes, I know, everyone is hitting me.
It's like a no-hands, no-footwork free live show,
I don't know what to call it,
It became like a routine,
I had never done it before,
I had never done it before, but maybe at the first Mu-Ashigeki Free Live,
I was kind of slapped on the back,
I thought it would get me fired up,
I thought it would get me fired up, so I had him do it.
Who always pats you on the back?
I don't know.
It doesn't hurt when it's Yono-chan,
No good,
I can't do it.
Cocona's is fine,
It even affects my internal organs.
Cocona seems to be relentless, really.
It's really, really annoying.Really, it's just enough to make you oohed and aahed.
That's just right.
Ahhh.
I don't get it at all. You are an athletic person, aren't you? You're a gymnast.
Yuuno hits the floor to keep from falling down. Yuuno always gets hit twice.
So after I hit him once, he says, "One more time. Then he hits me really hard.
He taps me twice a lot. Ah....
How about you, Mr. Maigo? How is your tour going?
Me? The tour is the same as usual.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
As usual.
That's what I'm talking about, a 10-year-plus player.
But that's why I don't want to spoil the tour for you,
The setlist feels like we did when we were teenagers.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up,
There's no place to rest.
Setlists are tough, aren't they?
Yes, setlists are hard.
The setlist is hard.
Also, the audience was finally able to speak out,
It's fun to see the audience shouting with energy.
I can feel the passion.
At the same time, I also felt that it was thanks to the audience's participation,
I feel like the audience, I don't know, the generation has changed.
That's true.
How do you feel?
Until now, there were always people in front of the audience,
But I feel that this has changed depending on the local information.
So I think that the best people, especially, are in the vicinity of the best people,
The best people are the ones who have not risen to the occasion.
The best are probably already looking at it.
Yes, I often see people who are overwhelmed.
I think that if they could see it up close, they would probably just watch it.
It's not that they want to get excited. They just want to watch.
I think it's a great thing to see the best in front of you without anything else.
It's true.
No, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That, something like that, so it's fun these days to tease those fans.
When I give them a little lesson, you know, a little something,
I'm thinking how cute they are.
I also like to ask them, "How are you doing today? How are you doing today?
It's nice, isn't it?
The clientele's enthusiasm.
The joint corner.
It's interesting.
With that kind of thing, Corona has finally calmed down and come back to life.
But there are only 5 shows left.
You finally experienced 2 days for the first time since you joined Ebitu.
The day in Osaka was the first time for both of us.
We had never performed at consecutive shows, so we were very nervous that day.
We had not done two days in a long time.
Our bodies were tense.
Before that, there was a 2-week gap, right?
Two weeks had passed.
Before Osaka
I felt a complete swing.
I'm sure I'll perform well today.
It's not that I had a bad day before that.
I was just stretching carefully like that.
And then two of them, two of them were like...
I can't go at all today.
It hurts.
Yukari, you were sitting down.
I didn't stretch at all.
You said it was the front bone of the ilium.
The anterior ilium.
Your grip hasn't progressed either.
I'm a soft person as it is.
You're right, you're right.
I'm always pretty flabby.
But that day...
I couldn't move forward from a sitting position.
I couldn't bend my legs.
I thought to myself, "We've been doing this for two days.
I thought that everyone had to do this for two days.
I mean, they did it for two days in a row, didn't they?
That's amazing.
I made you say it.
This time, though...
There was one thing that I felt was a little different
There's one thing that's a little different this time.
You've got other things on your schedule.
I'm on tour.
During the tour...
I mean...
I'm trying to have a schedule that allows me to focus on the tour.
I think it's because we're all students.
From your point of view.
Yes, from a sister's point of view
From an idol NEET point of view
From a neat idol point of view.
That's what it's like
You know...
You know, school life and stuff.
It's hard... to have both.
That's right.
I know.I knew it.
It's called a report.
I have a bit of a nasty hair.
Have you ever heard of a report?
Have you?
The reports.
They're due by a certain date.
I usually get five or six at a time.
One month.
I'll fix it by reading them in.
What's wrong with the sound?
I don't know if you're asking me to load them for you.
It's like the sound is starting to get off.
If you're having trouble with the sound.
Please reload the file.
That should fix it.
Is there a report?
Yes, there is.
I have to do five or six a month.
That's a lot of work.
Five or six a month?
Five or six a month.
I get one a week.
Some weeks I get two.
Five or six a fortnight.
In a month, we don't have ten.
That's right.
There are a lot of them.
But...
I have lessons in Ebichu.
I have to learn how to dance.
I have to learn to sing.
And I also have to do radio work.
I'm stretched a lot.
I'm getting stretched a lot.
The more time I have to do
The more you have to do, the more you want to do.
The more you have to do, the more you want to put it off.
That's right.
With your mom...
We decided to do one a day.
And then...
I said yes.
But...
I should do it.
I can't do it anymore.
A piece a day like that
So I hid it, hid it, hid it.
I've been hoarding dozens and dozens of them.
And then...
Two days ago.
Two days before I submitted it.
My mom found out.
I was on summer vacation.
And the next time Yuna and I
I promised Yuna to go out with her next time.
That's right.
But my mom found out.
I couldn't tell her that I was going to go out with her.
Let's go to Yuna the day before.
That's the worst!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about that, too.
I'll call you at 23:56.
What?
And on that day...
He said he wanted to go to Asakusa.
I'd made a reservation to rent a kimono.
So...
Before that
While we were on the way...
Are you sure you want to go tomorrow?
I said no, not for two days.
Like it's too hard.
And you had plans before Osaka.
Two days.
After.
That's why it's too hard.
So I asked her if she wanted to cancel tomorrow.
I was like, "Yeah, let's go.
Later.
When I got home...
I said, "I'm sorry, I can't do it.
And at that time...
I didn't tell him I was pissed off about the report.
Oh, so you're just a slacker.
I'm sick. My feet and neck hurt.
Why?
I said I wouldn't stop.
Why don't you tell a lie on top of a lie?
But...
The report...
I knew it hurt you to do it.
I knew it.
So you're going to tell Yuna...
Yuna, too.
I thought Yuna probably didn't do the reports, either.I thought Yuna probably wasn't doing reports either.
I wanted to be a character that said I was doing reports.
What kind of person are you?
I'm sorry, I'm not feeling well.
My ankle hurts, so I told her I'd be close.
That sucks.
That's terrible.
It's terrible, isn't it?
But I thought maybe Yuna and I could meet.
That's the schedule.
There's another one.
I'm not sure which one was a lie after all.
And then the next day...
Suddenly, nothing really happened.
There was no reason for it to happen.
On line.
YoonA, are you really going to graduate from high school?
I said...
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute.
I'm going to finish high school.
That's so funny.
What the hell is that?
I was going to go on an influx, but...
My mom was really pissed at me about the report.
She's really upset about it.
She said, "If you can't focus that well...
I can quit if I can't concentrate that much.
School?
School.
That's what she said.
That's why I'm here.
I'm talking about the 5 or 6 people in the Takanaka report.
When I quit school...
I was a little shaken when they told me I could advertise on M-Chu.
I was a little shaken.
I'm not wavering.
That's not rocking the boat.
You're spending too much time on it.
But I wanted to have friends.
And I wanted to go to school.
To Yuna.
I asked her if she was going to finish high school. I asked her.
She said I would finish high school.
So I thought, "Well, I'll do my best now.
Then I thought...
I thought maybe she was mad at me for the report.
I got stabbed.
That's smart.
Maybe I didn't do the report.
I didn't do the report and I got mad at him.
Yeah! Like that.
I got stung.
What?
I got stabbed.
Don't use complicated words.
He's on to us.
I'm on your radar.
I knew I should have told Yuna.
She's mad at me.
That's so funny.
That's amazing.
Really...
I'm serious.
What if Yuna says she's not graduating?
I guess I'll just go.
You think she'll go? Will I leave?
But what shocked me...
I didn't get in as many reports as Emma did.
What?
Huh?
That's why Emma...
Wait a minute... this is getting into another issue.
Emma didn't turn in her report.
She's mad she didn't go to Asakusa.
I didn't turn in my report.
So we were just saying it was a good thing.
So it was a good day to do lots of things.
That's right.
The day I went to Asakusa, I went to Tokyo Dome by myself.
Wait, wait, wait, you didn't do the report and you went?
I did.
You did? I did.
I did it, and I rode the roller coaster by myself.
What? Wait, wait, wait. Wait, you went by yourself?
I went by myself, but I really wanted to play.
I had to go by myself. I had to play.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Alone.
Alone at the amusement park?
Why? Maybe because there's no admission fee.
No, no, no.
It's per attraction.
Per attraction.
That's why I only wanted to go on the roller coaster.
I just wanted to ride the roller coaster and go home.
We started doing it at the Tokyo Dome.
It was great.
I mean, it was hot, but...
But I don't know.But what is it?
I just finished taking a bath.
When I was told I couldn't go...
I'm wearing a kimono tomorrow, and we're playing.
I was really into it.
I was ready to play.
Why didn't you just support another girl?
I didn't want to.
You didn't like it?
I don't have any friends at school yet.
Oh, because you wanted to go.
I wanted to go.
Don't stop for a second.
The rest of the team, too.
Maybe I'll ask you out before.
That's right.
He's a NEET.
He's back, isn't he?
That's a bit much.
That's out of line.
I'm kind of cool with it.
I called him the day after the gig.
I wondered who would come.
But I really wanted to go.
So I went alone.
I don't think I'd go by myself after that.
But I only rode the roller coaster once.
I'll just ride it once and go home.
Wow.
I'm so happy to be able to do it alone.
Lately, the staff has been talking about what's the hardest thing to do by yourself.
Ah...
I can't do Disneyland by myself.
Oh, I went there.
Yasu said, I've been there with Yasu.
Yasu and I were talking like we've been there at all.
If you have an annual pass or something.
I just told him that I couldn't believe why he would go to Disneyland if he had an annual pass or something like that.
I thought the hardest thing for me to do was to go to French restaurant alone.
Same thing, only I couldn't do Disneyland and French food at that time.
Hmmm.
I'll go for a course meal alone.
I'm afraid to go alone for a course meal.
Huh.
But the food, though. But it's just served in order.
If you put your mind to it, it's fine.
The amusement park, because there's a line, right? Disneyland?
There's a line.
I've been pushing all day at Disneyland. I'm on my cell phone.
I was carrying.
And when it's my turn, I have a cigarette.
But it's fun to talk while you wait.
How's that?
If I went alone...
Surprisingly, everyone talks, but not all the time.
They say Disney is a place where couples break up.
That's a misnomer.
Every couple that goes to Disney breaks up.
Stop it. Stop it.
A lot of people break up because... because everyone goes.
Because everyone goes, the probability is high.
There's a high probability.
Also, it's crowded.
It's crowded.
It's crowded. I said I wanted to ride it.
How long is the ride, like an hour or two?
Last Saturday, was it last Saturday?
It was the longest day of the week.
It was one of the busiest days of the year.
It was like a six-hour wait for some attraction.
It was trending.
But if we're gonna be in the same place for six hours, we're gonna have to split up.
We're breaking up.
I'll break up with a guy who's that unorganized.
I'd call it a bad arrangement.
Maybe if you get a Fastpass or something.
If I get a Fastpass, I can go.
But waiting in line is part of the fun.
Six hours. Six hours. Can we talk?
Six hours.
I don't think so.
Maybe I can.
I can do it.
I'll be working with Tsu-chan, the manager.
I'm a regular once a month at a hangout in Akita.
I've been playing "Ebiichi" with Tsu-chan's manager at a hangout in Akita.
We talked about how we're trending.
We talked for a long time.
We talked for a total of 8 hours.
You were with us the whole time on the Yasumoto tour.
With Tsuda.
Tsuda talked the whole time.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're not Tsuda.
That's him.
Oh, I see.
You're right, Tsuda's great.
Even if we go out to eat, it's full, right?
What would you do?
What if there are no chairs in the tray?If tray phones didn't have chairs and stuff.
I'd be a frog.
We'd be surrounded.
What? No, no, no, no, no!
That's lame.
I can't help it.
They don't all have reservations in the wards.
There's a reservation system for cherry blossoms and such, but...
That's for sure.
Have you two been to the amusement park?
Yes, they have.
You've been to this one or that one, right?
Yes, we have.
But the food...
Morning breeze...
Oh, so it was a morning breeze after Maoji.
That's why I was looking forward to it.
I was looking forward to it too, but...
My mom just walked in.
Don't blame others.
Oh no...
You're so funny!
Emai, the kids are close too.
But I was planning to go with Eman
I spent the money for Asakusa at Tokyo Domicity.
I asked her to put it off for a month.
That's for April.
It's fine, if it's in the summer after the tour.
Why don't you wear a yukata or something in the evening?
Sure...
Wouldn't that be great? Asakusa...
Asakusa is so nice.
It's great.
What?
What? I didn't understand what you just said.
You're right, Emma...
No, no, no, he's talking and he's not telling me the end of the word.
It's when he starts talking about endings that it gets complicated.
I'm right next to you at the concert.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
He never says it out loud.
I'm saying it out loud.
So, the other day in Osaka...
The title of this tour
Private Ebisu Aggregation 100%.
Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebizumu.
I said "100% Ebizum! I said "100% Ebizum!
I don't know why, but they look so smug over here!
I always say before rehearsal
I always say "Good morning, good morning!
I always go in as if to say "Good morning.
Mayu always smiles at me when she's next to me.
I thought, "I'm definitely going to do it today.
I looked at her with a smug look on my face.
To Mayu
I could tell.
It's the same at school. You have to be conscious of it.
That's right!
Lately, I've been in the middle of a boom.
I'm going to imitate a picture.
I love you
and
Yuuna's
Yes?
Yes, I love you.
That's why I've been trying to reply properly lately.
Yes.
That's great.
Everyone is copying me.
Yeah, it makes me want to do it.
Yeah, it's like that.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
She looked like she was about to cry.
It makes me want to do it.
Okay, then.
Yuna, can we move on?
I think so.
Okay, today.
I know I called it a loose distribution, but...
I have an announcement.
Well, what do you think?
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
This year's Nakaon
will not be held this year!
What!
Not even once!
We won't be a part of it.
Why not?
He said, "Yay.
What?
He said he did it.
It's a mid-tone.
It's got a middle.
Oh, first.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yay.
Huh?
Oh, you poor thing.
What?
What did he say?
Two of us have never done it before.
Well, unfortunately...
There will be no Chunyun in Ebichu this year.
But instead...
I would like to try something new.
We are going to try something new this year.
This year's autumn event is
Shrimp City Junior High School
Okera Disco 2023 will be held!
Yay!
After this, at 20:00, you can see the details of the event.
This year, we are going to hold a live concert titled "Okera Disco 2023".
We will be holding two live concerts on two different days.
The first one is in Kanagawa, October 7, at Pacifico Yokohama National Hall.
The second day will be held at Tokyo International Hall up Hall A on October 22.
Congratulations!
Do you know what Okera Disco is?
What is it?
Okela Disco?
Excuse me.
What is it?
Okela Disco?
Okela Disco.
It looks cool.
It looks cool, doesn't it?
I think there is a teacher here who knows more about this than we do.
What's that?
Stop it. Stop it.
It's more than we can explain.
Who are you here for?
We're not here today to sample Pamien's passportm tamura.
That's all.
We are not here for the cold ramen.
So, please, let the three of you explain.
I should have prepared it properly.
I'm having them come for that snack.
No, I thought it was an explanation that I was going to stand up and half-heartedly turn on the rocker.
No, no, no.
Okela disco is orchestra that calls itself orchestra.
Disco equals dance music.
Music all over your fingers with an orchestra,
Let's get wrapped up in a wave of sound that will have you swaying your body and enjoying your own groove.
It is a concept that replaces the word of advice. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
So that's what this is all about.
Yes, that's right.
What was that you were saying about the middle tone?
Oh, dear.
I don't understand.
It's difficult.
Do you guys understand?
Yes, I do.
Dancing midtones.
That's right. To put it simply, it's a dancing midtone,
But there are two differences from the Chūon,
The first is that the Chūon was a seated performance,
The first is that while the Chūon was seated, this time there are seats for people standing,
Of course, there are also seats in a seated position.
The other is that at the mid-tone, you were not allowed to speak out.
But this time, you can speak up.
Yay!
Yay! Just like at a disco. Like at a disco.
I've never said it before.
I don't really know what disco is either.
It's a live concert where you can dance, sing, and talk,
But it is a live performance where you can dance, sing, and even talk,
The same point as the middle tone is the penlight,
Now, Mr. Yoochoo is here,
Penlights will not be available due to production reasons. So I wonder what it will be like.
So I wonder what it will be like.
What do you think it will be like?
It's going to be fun.
It looks like fun.
I don't know, I don't know,
I wonder if it's going to be orchestral, or EDM, or something like that.
It's cool.
It looks cool.
And the megaphone?
Oh, Emma's megaphone.
How about Emma's megaphone?
How's the megaphone?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Please put it on in the second.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure.
Something like that.
I'll wear a tuxedo or something.
That's nice.
I'd like to do a concert with a dress code for the audience.
I'd like to do that.
Sure, I'd like that.
This is different, but the customers too.
We don't do that at Okkelaitisco.
I'd like to see all the customers come dressed like that.
Sure, like the background music of "How are you doing today?
Like that kind of thing.I had a different impression of him.
It was a very different impression.
It was very different from the usual.
I like the idea of a live concert with a dress code.
Sounds interesting.
I'll try it next time.
I'll give it a try next time.
You know, everyone at that time..,
It was so different from what we usually do,
I didn't know what was going on.
I didn't know who was who.
It was like a fun dress code.
Heh.
Well, there was a live concert.
And you got tickets this time, too,
Yes, there are two types of tickets,
First, there are reserved seats, seated seats, and Kauner seats.
The first one is reserved seats and seated seats, and the second one is Kauner seats,
The first is reserved seats and seated seats,
Yes, there are,
The seats are within the front 5 rows.
So you will definitely be in the front,
You can see the shrimp tureen.
Nice.
Great.
It's close.
It feels good over here, doesn't it?
The expensive one, yes.
It's a little expensive,
But, you know,
I think it's worth going to see,
Like Pacifico Yokohama or Tokyo International Holler,
It's a big box like the ones we use for our tour finale,
It's a big box,
So we will be in the front 5 rows,
Oh my god.
Oh my god,
I want to take pictures.
Let's film it.
Shall we look at it?
Let's see.
I want to see it.
I want to see.
I want to see it,
I hope you will all enjoy it,
I hope you are looking forward to it.
Let's see..,
This is it?
After this, after this,
June 22nd,
8:00 p.m,
Uh..,
Tickets,
The fan club selection will begin.
The Black Tiger secret book selection will be held on June 22,
June 22,
Thursday, June 22nd, from 20:00 to July 4th, from 23:59,
until 23:59 on July 4th,
We hope you will all be able to participate,
I hope you will all come.
I would like to add a little more,
We have been working on something new and different for a long time, and we would like to show something new and different for everyone to see,
We will be working on it from now on, so please come and see how it will turn out.
There is a possibility that it will be a one-time-only event.
Haha.
If it is good, it will continue.
You know what, I didn't say that.
We will all come back to the center again.
I might go back.
No, really, I'd like to make it something totally different. It is more interesting to have differences.
I would like to pursue the advantages of Chuo for Chuo and Okera Disco for Okera Disco.
There is a strong voice saying that we should do both.
It's very hard to do it twice.
It's a lot of work.
So I am not saying that we won't do it in the future.
This time, with the addition of Emina, Bichu itself has grown to 10 members, and I hear that it has become more fun,
So, we decided to make a new attempt to create a more enjoyable disco.
So we decided to make a new attempt at the Okera Disco.
Ha-ha-ha.
But I'm really looking forward to it.
They showed me an image of what it will look like. It looks like this.
This is how I want the concert to be.
I really wanted to do this.
I like the middle sound, but I haven't experienced the middle sound.
You haven't experienced the middle tone. But I like it better when it's raised. It's not there yet.
That's for sure.
It was really cool.
It was great.
I can't wait to see it.
That was awesome.
Some of the comments were a little bit like, "Oh, this is what it looks like," but there were people who were close.
There were.
Yes, there were.
Even if there is no dress code, I'll wear it in the cab.
Oh.Oh.
That's very good.
That's very good. It's certainly cool because it's a box.
Yes, yes. Muse Park in Chichiru is always affected by the weather,
There are a lot of rainy girls in Ebichu, right?
The lawn and Ebichu are always soaked with rain.
The lawn is still better, though.
Actually, there is a part of the seats with a roof that leaks, and it's dripping down in a concentrated manner, and it's outrageous, you know.
I just wanted to find a place.
Oh yeah, I found a customer in the middle of a gig.
I love it there, too. I love the center, but...
I hope we can all dance like crazy this time.
Yes, we're looking forward to it!
It's suddenly quiet.
There are a lot of events happening this year.
I'm also starting to do a little bit of work on the Famien, but I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it!
Mr. Yamayagiwa, can you say something that will make people want to come here from summer to fall?
From summer to fall
First of all, we have the Fami En too.
So, don't miss the live concerts and other events.
I'll make sure to finish my work and assignments.
Definitely come to see me!
I'll be waiting for you.
You don't have to say that.
I'll finish first so I can get on the gig.
Thank you very much.
Come on in, guys.
Well, let's all enjoy this summer and fall together.
You're so cute sometimes.
You're really cute.
The guy next to me was kind of a jerk.
I thought you weren't.
But if you're serious, I'm sure they'll come.
But I'm not... I'm just saying, you know, you can do it with me.
I'm not going either way.
So I'll be waiting for you.
Well, I'd better get going.
See you next week.
This one by Maya...
It's good.
I knew you'd do it, too, Maya
As we move from summer to fall, I'd like to show this to all of you.
August 5th and 6th are
BiTCHU Summer Family Yeas
genus abbreviated as Family Yeas
in Yamanakako 2023.
This year, we will be at the Pakupaku Utan Village.
We're going to have the Shinya Muscle Cafe again this year!
I'm talking without permission.
Without the permission of adults
I'm talking without permission
We'll have cold ramen and
And a protein shake.
I'm going to start eating.
I have a lot of prototypes that I'm not ready to eat.
But I'm preparing something delicious.
And you know, at the Okella Disco
Through such a full summer
We're going to release a lot of love
I'll be waiting for you
Yes, sir.
Yay!
I've taken the liberty of announcing it.
I've made the announcement.
Did you finish the long acquaintance yet?
It's over.
Oh, it's already over?
Thank you very much for the long acquaintance.
For the family
First of all, we have a spring tour coming up.
We will do our best to make it happen.
We only have tickets for this week.
That's right.
Tokyo Electron Hall
Tokyo Electron Hall in Miyagi
Miyagi
No, no, no.
Like Disneyland.
Yes.
But we couldn't hold Miyagi last year.
Because of the venue.
So...
It's been a while.
Well, I just went to DICE's live 2-man show instead of you.
I went to DICE's live 2-man show, so...
I may have met you there, but...
But it's been a long time since I've seen you at Wan Wan.
I hope you all enjoy the show.
Ten Fingers in the Middle is really good, isn't it?
I'm sure we'll be there.
I'm sure we'll be in the same prefecture.
We're looking forward to seeing you!
And that's that.
Oh, yes! On June 30th...
Let's see...
Night Fever
Um, what's the word?Let's see, what do you call it?
Friday
Friday Night Fever
Let's see...
Kyozin-san and Hansi-san's
Opening of the match
Live
We will be live up before the game.
Please look forward to what song they will play!
I'm looking forward to seeing you all!
Please look forward to seeing what you will look like.
I hope you all
I hope you can come.
Tickets are sold out.
I saw that the other day.
That day, the Osshiko Club...
That's right! Rielly's going to throw it.
Yeah!
Rielly's the star of the show.
Yes, yes, yes.
She's going to throw it!
That's a lot of stuff, isn't it?
Yeah.
The day before that...
Risch's breakup concert.
I see.
Yeah.
And the day after that, I thought, "What's going on?
Oh!
I feel a little emo emo, but by all means, everyone.
I'm looking forward to baseball. Not baseball, the dome.
The Dome. I'm looking forward to it. Tokyo Dome.
It's your first time. Yeah, it's the first time for both of us.
But, shrimp, does the Dome have police cars?
No, we don't have a dome in Tokyo Dome. Only Seibu Dome.
And that was during the Seppu Exchange Games.
Yeah, I missed it, like 16 years ago.
Yeah, so...
Do you have any support hashtags?
For baseball?
Baseball.
Well, we'll think of something in the meantime.
By then?
Can we think of something by then?
You want me to ask you two to think about it? Now.
Cheer, cheer, cheer!
Good luck, Ebitu!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Hashtag Ebichu go for it!
It's not a hashtag, it's "Go Ebichu!
June 30 is the hashtag Ebichu Ganbare!
Is "Ganbare" in hiragana?
It's in hiragana.
Ebichu Ganbare!
This seems to have a lot of lift.
I've seen it in a lot of places.
Ebichu go for it!
Like the spring tour.
When the members of EBITCHU were on TV
EBITCHU, go for it!
Ebichu, go for it!
It's like a club offafee.
ahaha
Go Ebitchew!
That's a good one.
Good luck, Ebitchew!
I look forward to working with you!
I'll be glad to meet you.
Okay, so...
If you're coming on the 30th...
If you are coming on the 30th, please look forward to it, and if you are coming on the spring tour, please look forward to it too!
And today's event
Big disc 2023
About 20 minutes after this
Tickets will be sold out in about 20 minutes.
If you come in now, you'll still make it in time, right?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Can we get this over with?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm writing something.
Someone said Tokyo Dome.
Oh, Tokyo.
Tokyo
Dome
Oh, oh, oh
This is Sho Yamamoto's
I did it with this.
Then he said, "Good luck with the hashtag Ebichu!
Tokyo Dome by all means
with the hashtag
I think I'm going to write a hashtag
with both.
If there's no space, it's just a hashtag Tokyo Dome.
Without space, it's just the hashtag Tokyo Dome.
Certainly.
KyotoKyoto
Kyoto means Kyoto
Can I use composite hashtags?
If it's an underscore, it works, doesn't it?
Yes, you can use underbar.
If you use Tokyo underbar dome, it's Tokyo Dome.
Oh, sure.
Certainly.
You can't do it!
What?
What should I do?
Tokyo Under Bird Dome
I mean Tokyo Dome
I've been thinking about it until the 5th
Tokyo Dome
You're right.
You're right, Mr. Suge.
As it is...
It's just Tokyo Dome.
Just hang in there, everyone.
Just hang in there.
Easy to understand
If you need anything, Shinjuku, please look at Twitter
I'm looking forward to working with you
Yes, sir.
Well then, that's all for us.
We have arrived at Shinjuku.
Thank you very much.